What are some of the things that annoy you the most about AI?
That I think it is making people dumber because they're choosing not to think
and they're letting AI make their decisions but then they have no context into why decisions
were made to begin with because they weren't the ones who did the thinking.
I hate that so much of the world has almost immediately become AI slop.
Like every caption on Instagram, I mean thank you messages that I get from people,
people leaving testimonials.
Biggest thing you can detect with it is forced negation and staccato sentences,
meaning it's not this or this or this but that or it's not because this it's because
it's because this is this is this is so they'll do this repetition of sentence structure and
it gets really really annoying and so most times you can take a paragraph of that and
just turn it into a sentence of like what the fuck are you trying to say and then just say that.